<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GEM</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Visit activity -->
    <!-- Main Hall activity -->
    <string name="main_hall">Main Hall\nopen today untill 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="main_hall_title">MAIN HALL</string>
    <string name="main_hall_opened">Open seven days</string>
    <string name="main_hall_openedTime">
        <item>Sunday - Thursday : 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
        <item>\nFirday and Saturday: 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
    </string>
    <string name="main_hall_vacations">
        <item>Closed Prophet Mohammed\'s Birthday</item>
        <item>\nThursday, November 30,2017</item>
    </string>
    <string name="main_hall_location">
        <item>Alexandria Desert Rd, Kafr Nassar</item>
        <item>\nAl Haram, Giza Governante</item>
        <item>\n+202 3377 68 96</item>
    </string>
    <!-- Main 2 activity -->
    <string name="second_hall">Main 2\nopen today untill 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="second_hall_title">MAIN HALL</string>
    <string name="second_hall_opened">Open seven days</string>
    <string name="second_hall_openedTime">
        <item>Sunday - Thursday : 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
        <item>\nFirday and Saturday: 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
    </string>
    <string name="second_hall_vacations">
        <item>Closed Prophet Mohammed\'s Birthday</item>
        <item>\nThursday, November 30,2017</item>
    </string>
    <string name="second_hall_location">
        <item>Alexandria Desert Rd, Kafr Nassar</item>
        <item>\nAl Haram, Giza Governante</item>
        <item>\n+202 3377 68 96</item>
    </string>
    <!-- Main 3 activity -->
    <string name="third_hall">Main 3\nopen today untill 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="third_hall_title">MAIN HALL</string>
    <string name="third_hall_opened">Open seven days</string>
    <string name="third_hall_openedTime">
        <item>Sunday - Thursday : 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
        <item>\nFirday and Saturday: 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
    </string>
    <string name="third_hall_vacations">
        <item>Closed Prophet Mohammed\'s Birthday</item>
        <item>\nThursday, November 30,2017</item>
    </string>
    <string name="third_hall_location">
        <item>Alexandria Desert Rd, Kafr Nassar</item>
        <item>\nAl Haram, Giza Governante</item>
        <item>\n+202 3377 68 96</item>
    </string>
    <!-- Main 4 activity -->
    <string name="fourth_hall">Main 4\nopen today untill 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="fourth_hall_title">MAIN HALL</string>
    <string name="fourth_hall_opened">Open seven days</string>
    <string name="fourth_hall_openedTime">
        <item>Sunday - Thursday : 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
        <item>\nFirday and Saturday: 10:00AM - 6:00PM</item>
    </string>
    <string name="fourth_hall_vacations">
        <item>Closed Prophet Mohammed\'s Birthday</item>
        <item>\nThursday, November 30,2017</item>
    </string>
    <string name="fourth_hall_location">
        <item>Alexandria Desert Rd, Kafr Nassar</item>
        <item>\nAl Haram, Giza Governante</item>
        <item>\n+202 3377 68 96</item>
    </string>

    <!-- Highlight activity -->
    <string name="highlights_must_see">The Must-Sees</string>
    <string name="highlights_must_see_items">Browse few of the GEM\'s most\ncompelling works\n</string>
    <string name="highlights_family_favorites">\nFamily Favorites</string>
    <string name="highlights_family_favorites_items">You may want to check some\nof the most family vaforites\n</string>

    <!-- Artifacts details activity -->
    <!-- Artifact 1 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_1">TUT ANKAMUN MASK</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_1">This mask of Tutankhamun is an example of the high est artistic and technical achievements of the an-cient Egyptians in the New Kingdom.
        \nCovering the head of the wrapped mummy in its coffin and activated by a magical spell, no.151b from the Book of the Dead, the mask ensured more pro-tection for the king\'s body.
        \nThe exact portrayal of the king\'s facial features achieved here made it possible for his soul to recog nize him and return to his mummified body, thus en uring his resurrection.
        \nhe head is covered by the royal headdress and the forehead bears the emblems of kingship and protec tion: the vulture and uraeus, or cobra.
        \nThe gold sheets used in this wonderful mask are joinec together by heating and hammering. The eyes are of obsidian and quartz and the eyebrows and eyelids are inlaid with lapis lazuli. The broad inlaid collar of semiprecious stones and colored glass ends in falcon heads.
        \nDimensions: Height 54 cm Width 39.3 cm</string>

    <!-- Artifact 2 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_2">Sphinx of Amenhotep the Second</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_2">A sphinx has the body and strength of a lion and the head or face of a man, symbolizing wisdom and intelligence.
        \nThe ancient Egyptians sculpted different kinds of sphinxes with a human head, a ram head, or a human face with the mane of a lion. Sphinxes represent various deities, especially Amun-Re, identified with the kings who reigned when the sphinxes were made. 
        \nThe human heads or faces usually have the facial features of these kings. This sphinx portrays King Amenhotep the Second.
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 3 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_3">Anubis Carrying the Moon Disk</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_3">Anubis, the black jackal, was the animal that personified the deity who was believed to protect the cemetery, and thus became the patron deity of mummification. Anubis was depicted in funerary scenes guiding the deceased to Osiris in the court of justice. Embalmers performing the mummification of the corpses wore jackal masks.
        \nIn the legend of the divine birth of Queen Hatshepsut and King Amenhotep the third, Anubis is represented rolling or bringing the disk of the moon and wishing the young royal children long life. In modern times, ceremonies performed on the seventh day of a child\'s birth contain a step, in which the newly born child is put in a sieve and is shaken and asked to "obey his mother and not to obey his father."
        \nthis cartonnage piece, the jackal-headed god comes, carrying the disk of the moon, and wishing the deceased long life. He wears a gilded collar, an unusual short kilt with a long tail hanging from the front and sandals. A long, wide white drapery hangs from behind and reaches the feet.
        \nDimensions:  Width 13.5 cm  Height 33.5 cm
    </string>

    <!-- Artifact 4 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_4">Shawabti of Tutankhamun</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_4">The Shawabti, or funerary, figures were intended to perform work in the place of the deceased in the afterlife. They were usually made of faience, wood, or pottery and were various sizes.
        \nThey were divided according to their functions and to the Egyptian calendar as follows: 365 workmen, each for one day of the year, and 36 overseers, each as a chief of a week of ten days or ten workers. In the tomb of Tutankhamun, 12 supplementary foremen were added, one for each month, totaling 413.
        \nThis Shawabti of gilded wood is an image of the young king wearing the Khepresh crown of ceremonies and processions and the uraeus. It is adorned with a broad collar cut in gold leaf and the two insignia of Osiris.
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 5 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_5">Crocodile God Sobek</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_5">The River Nile and the canals were the main roads of ancient Egypt, although sailing was a great risk because of the crocodiles and hippopotami. Egyptians, therefore, wanted to ward off the danger from crocodiles. They built temples for the cult of the crocodile god Sobek at Esna, Kom Ombo, the Faiyum region, and other places. Each temple had a pool or small underground chambers, in which a live crocodile was kept to receive the offerings and prayers.
        \nSobek was associated with the sun god Re. In the Book of the Dead, spells were compiled for the deceased person "for driving off the crocodile that comes to take away the deceased\'s magic from him in the realm of the dead" (spell 31).
        \nThis statue was placed in one of the god\'s temples by a pious worshipper. It was easy to pray and place offerings in front of the statue. The figure, together with the base, was cut from a single block. The mouth is closed, and the details of the body were carved in relief, crossed and striped. Few details, however, can be seen on the figure.
        \nDimensions:  Length 9 cm  Height 6.5 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 6 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_6">Goddess Isis Nursing Her Son Horus</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_6">Isis was the wife of the god Osiris and mother of the falcon god Horus. The divine triad was one of the most important and famous groups of deities in ancient Egypt. Isis was often represented nursing her son Horus and became the symbol of motherhood and protection. She was also the goddess of charm and protected people from evil and from magic.
        \nThis is a statue of the goddess carrying the child Horus and nursing him in a symbolic way. In this form, she was also identified with the cow Hathor, the mother goddess. There is a similarity between the statues of Isis nursing her son Horus and the later Christian images of the Madonna and Child. On the goddess\'s head are the two horns of the cow Hathor with the sun disk between them.
        \nDimensions:  Height 32 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 7 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_7">Outer Coffin of Queen Meritamun</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_7">This giant coffin of Queen Meritamun, wife of Amenhotep the First of the Eighteenth Dynasty, is considered to be one of the finest coffins ever made in Egypt. It depicts the deceased queen, wearing a long wig, the ends of which with their two locks almost reach her chest.
        \nHer arms are crossed on her chest; each hand holds a lotus scepter, which is the symbol of resurrection. A collar with incised parallel lines shows between the locks of hair. The rest of the lid is decorated with long parallel feather designs.
        \nThese designs are exquisitely carved directly into the wood, rather than being modeled or inscribed on the gesso, or plaster of Paris covering, of the coffin.
        \nIn the center of the lid there is a long vertical painted hieroglyphic inscription. It invokes the god Osiris to grant offerings to the queen and "every beautiful and pure thing and the sweet breath of the North".
        \nDimensions:  Length 3.1 cm  Width 87 cm

    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 8 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_8">Bust of Amenemhat the Third in Priestly Costume</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_8">This is the upper part of a gray granite, larger than life-size statue of King Amenemhat the Third. It depicts the king as a high priest wearing the panther skin.
        \nThe high cheekbones, wrinkled face, and bitter, pouted mouth identify the statue as belonging to the Twelfth Dynasty ruler, King Amenemhat the Third. This statue had been formerly attributed to a Hyksos king of the Seventeenth Dynasty.
        \nThis statue portrays the king as standard-bearer for the first time.
        \nThis depiction was frequently used in the later Ramesside period.
        \nDimensions:  Height 100 cm  Width 99 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 9 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_9">Gold Mask Mummy Cover of King Psusennes the First</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_9">In this gold mask mummy cover, Psusennes the First appears with the royal headdress surmounted by the uraeus, or royal cobra. He wears a divine plaited false beard.
        \nThe mask is made of two pieces of beaten gold, soldered and joined together by five nails that can be seen from the back.
        \nThe king wears the royal Nemes headdress, usually made of linen, surmounted by the sacred uraeus, the royal cobra. This protected the king against his opponents and enemies in life and after death.
        \nThe king wears a divine plaited false beard, which is the symbol of dignity. He also wears a broad Usekh collar incised with floral decorations. The inlays of the eyelids and eyebrows and the straps fixing the beard are of glass paste. The eyes are made of black and white stone.
        \nDimensions:  Height 45 cm  Width 38 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 10 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_10">Gold Cover of Psusennes\' Mummy</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_10">This gold sheet covered the mummy of King Psusennes the first, who lived during the Twenty-First Dynasty. His tomb, which contained amazing treasures, was discovered at Tanis.
        \nThe mummy had been placed in three sarcophagi for protection. The smallest is made of silver; the second is made of black granite, and the third, and largest, is pink granite.
        \nA gold mask hid the face of the mummy and the body was covered with this sheet of gold, which is decorated in the center with a winged ram holding in his claws the shen signs, symbols of eternity.
        \nThe upper part of the cover, corresponding to the torso, is decorated with two hands holding the insignia of the god Osiris: the crook and the flail. The rest of the cover is decorated with simulated mummy bandages.
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 11 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_11">Queen Hatshepsut Offering to Osiris</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_11">On this flake, the artist intended to show respect for the queen\'s majesty and drew her as a masculine figure, kneeling and wearing the Khepresh helmet-like crown of ceremonies. She is offering two jars of wine and cool water to the god Osiris of the underworld (not shown).
        \nThe queen wears a collar and a short kilt fastened with a belt. The text refers to "Maat-Ka-Ra (the throne name of Hatshepsut) beloved of Osiris," and "offering wine and cool water". The drawing is brightly colored and the primarily red sketch lines, and some corrections in the proportions are shown.
        \nDimensions:  Width 8 cm  Height 15 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 12 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_12">Fragments of Standing Statue of a King</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_12">The statue portrays a king standing on a small base. His left leg is forward, in the tradition of Egyptian statuary. He wears the White Crown of Upper Egypt and the short royal kilt called the Shendyt. His left arm is by his side, the right arm is bent, and he is holding the royal mace.
        \nThe artist succeeded in carving the facial features and the ceremonial beard in this hard stone. Judging by its artistic style despite the bad state of its preservation, it is possible to attribute this statuette to King Nefer-ef-Re of the Fifth Dynasty.
        \nDimensions:  Height 21 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 13 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_13">Sarcophagus of Isis</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_13">Isis was the daughter of Khonsu and probably a second wife of Khabekhnet.
        \nThe coffin is made in the image of Isis. Her face is long. She wears an elaborately curled wig crowned by a wide floral headband. A large and colorful floral collar covers her entire chest and rosettes mark her breasts. Jewelry further enhances Isis\'s beauty. She wears earrings that are made of bone or ivory. She also has rings on her fingers and bracelets on her wrists.
        \nIsis is clothed with a long garment made of a single large piece of fringed linen. It was first wrapped around her torso, then draped over her shoulders and secured with a knot. In both hands, Isis clasps delicate tendrils of a creeper vine. This plant probably had a symbolic relationship with birth and rejuvenation.
        \nHieroglyphic inscriptions are written around the box and the lid.
        \nDimensions:  Length 190 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 14 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_14">Sarcophagus with Cover Depicting the Deceased</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_14">The sarcophagus is in the shape of a mummy. The cover portrays the deceased with all his accessories and his decorated shroud.
        \nHe wears a long wig reaching his chest that leaves the ears exposed. He also wears a false beard, and a large collar with many lines. Under the collar, a winged goddess and two eyes of Horus are depicted for his protection.
        \nHis hands are flat on his body, which is covered with many crossed hieroglyphic bands. The bands bear the magical formula from the Book of the Dead to protect the deceased.
        \nOn the bottom of the cover, Anubis, the god of mummification and the necropolis, is portrayed twice. The two depictions face each other.
        \nDimensions:  Height 70 cm  Length 250 cm  Width 90 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 15 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_15">Sarcophagus of Queen Kawit</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_15">The sarcophagus of Queen Kawit, who was the wife of King Montuhotep the Second, was one of the most noteworthy in terms of the low-relief sculpture in the Theban court.
        \nThe outer faces of this limestone sarcophagus are decorated with scenes from daily life, such as the queen applying makeup. Other scenes depict offerings and the afterlife.
        \nAt the place of Queen Kawit\'s head, there is a palace facade with the central doors decorated with Udjat eyes to permit the deceased to communicate with the world of living.
        \nThe elongated bodies and the coarse facial features reflect the Theban ideal of feminine beauty.
        \nDimensions:  Height 119 cm  Length 262 cm  Width 119 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 16 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_16">Amulet in the Shape of Winged Vulture</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_16">This amulet depicts the vulture Nekhbet, patron goddess of Upper Egypt. It is in the form of a miniature wide Usekh collar and is made of beaten gold with a counterweight. It was found among many pieces of jewelry belonging to King Psusennes the First.
        \nThe amulet was made to be hung on the king\'s garments by passing a wire or a string through a loop at the back of the amulet.
        \nThe details of the vulture\'s feathers, the wings and claws are all elaborately incised. The claws are holding the Shen rings of the universal power.
        \nDimensions:  Height 3.5 cm  Width 3.8 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 17 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_17">Sphinx of Amenemhat the Third</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_17">Seven sphinxes of Amenemhat were found in Tanis in the eastern Delta. They were thus called the Tanite sphinxes. They evoke the superhuman power of the king and emphasize his fearful appearance.
        \nThe vigorous face of the pharaoh is characterized by his prominent cheekbones, protuberant mouth and deeply furrowed cheeks, which create an effect of strength. Instead of the traditional Nemes headdress, his face is framed by a massive lion\'s mane that increases the sense of his majesty.
        \nThe statues rest on a tall and solid base decorated with cartouches of several sovereigns such as the Hyksos king Nehsy, Ramesses the Second, Merenptah and Psusennes, who all, over the centuries, usurped the group of sphinxes, fascinated by their idea. Egyptologists had mistankenly called them "the Hyksos sphinxes" because of their strange visage and the different names of the usurpers containing a Hyksos ruler too.
        \nDimensions:  Length 220 cm  Height 75 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 18 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_18">Meroitic Ba Statue of a Woman</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_18">This Ba statue depicts the soul as a bird with a human head. The statue depicts a lady with long wings standing on a flat pedestal that is slipped into a roughly executed base.
        \nHer facial features are defined by low relief lines that indicate the eyelids, the small smiling lips, and the large ears.
        \nThe three vertical cuts on each of her cheeks illustrate a Nubian custom. A round hole was cut on top of her head to hold a sun disk.
        \nShe wears a painted collar around her neck. The upper part of her body is nude and a long, wide skirt reveals only the front of her sandaled feet, which are carefully portrayed. Her arms are held to her sides and her right hand holds a cylindrical object.
        \nThe Ba statue was originally Egyptian, but placing this type of statue outside the tomb became common in Nubia.
        \nDimensions:  Height 66 cm  Length 44 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 19 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_19">Statue of In-Heret-Shu as a Mummy</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_19">The statue is one of several gilded wooden statues of deities found in the tomb of Tutankhamun. It depicts the god In-Heret-Shu standing on a rectangular base.
        \nHe is portrayed in the form of a mummy and his body is completely enveloped in a cloak. He wears a three-part wig on his head topped by four high feathers. His arms are crossed on his chest, which is adorned by a large pectoral. His body is entirely gilded, except for his eyes, eyebrows, and false beard.
        \nDimensions:  Height 74.5 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 20 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_20">Statue of Khufu-iam and his Wife</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_20">Khufu-iam and his wife are shown seated on a backless seat. The husband\'s hands are on his knees and he holds a small staff in his left hand. He wears a short curly wig covering his ears and a short overlapping kilt with wavy pleats, which was a fashionable garment during his period.
        \nHis wife sits next to him, resting her right arm on his right shoulder, a common pose in Ancient Egyptian statuary that shows strong family ties.
        \nShe wears a wide wig of medium length over her natural hair, which is partly visible.
        \nDimensions:  Height 45 cm  Width 27.5 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 21 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_21">Statue of the God Anubis with His Young Ones</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_21">The jackal was the sacred animal of the god Wepwawet and Anubis, the god of mummification. The sculpture of this sacred animal with his young ones is unique.
        \nThe group is portrayed on a rectangular base on which the jackal is lying on his side. Two of the four young jackals are held in his paws, one sits between the paw and the tail, and the other is held under the jackal\'s face.
        \nA scene of this type depicts the concept of paternal or maternal protection, which was synonymous with birth.
        \nDimensions:  Height 5 cm  Length 8 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 22 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_22">Statue of Goddess Hathor as a Cow</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_22">This statue of Hathor is a life-size depiction of a cow, her sacred animal. It was dedicated by Amenhotep the Second to Hathor and his father Tuthmosis the Third.
        \nThe cow is represented here coming out of the marshes as if to provide the deceased king with food offerings. Between her horns are the royal cobra uraeus, the sun disk, and two feathers. The cow\'s body has colored spots.
        \nThe small figure standing in front, beneath the cow\'s head, is that of the king. He is also depicted in relief being suckled by the cow to regain life and vitality.
        \nDimensions:  Height 2.2 cm  Length 2.3 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 23 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_23">Statue of a Uraeus</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_23">The uraeus, or royal cobra is fixed to a base. As always, the cobra is depicted with its hood extended, rearing up to powerfully strike any enemy of the king.
        \nOn its head, it wears the horns and the sun disk. In this form, the cobra is linked to the sun god Re as it surrounds his solar disk within its coils.
        \nIt also represents his fiery eye, which brings destruction to the hostile snakes of the underworld that might threaten the sun god on his nightly journey. The head and body are very well modeled.
        \nDimensions:  Length 121 cm
    </string>
    <!-- Artifact 24 details activity -->
    <string name="artifact_title_24">Statue of King Khafra</string>
    <string name="artifact_info_24">Khafra was one of the most famous kings of the Old Kingdom. He had many statues made of hard stone, which exhibit the marvelous skill of the artists during that time.
        \nThese statues were made to receive the offerings made to the king by his cult priests and courtiers. They were also used during funerary rituals such as the ceremonies of purification and the Opening of the Mouth. These ceremonies were performed symbolically beside the statues of the deceased king before and after his burial.
        \nHere, the king is represented on the throne with his names inscribed in a cartouche and the Serekh, or palace facade, on both sides of his legs. He is wearing the royal headdress, called the "Nemes" in Egyptian, and the royal Shendyt kilt.
        \nDimensions:  Height 120 cm
    </string>

    <!-- Staffpicks-->
    <string name="staff_art_of_statue">Art of statue</string>
    <string name="staff_art_of_statue_items">Browse our selections of the\nmost beatiful status\n</string>
    <string name="staff_favorite_selection">\nFavorite Selection</string>
    <string name="staff_favorite_selection_items">You may want to check some\nof the favories\n</string>


    <!--collection-->
    <string name="collection_str">Collections/</string>
    <string name="itemsNumber">50,000 record</string>
    <string name="filter_button">Filter</string>
    <string name="collection_kings">KINGS COLLECTIONS \n</string>
    <string name="collection_status">\nSTATUES COLLECTIONS \n</string>


    <string-array name="lang_array">
        <item>ENGLISH</item>
        <item>العربيه</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Pages name-->
    <string name="title_activity_visit">Visit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_artifactsDetails">Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_collections">Collections</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="title_activity_clothes">Clothes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_artifacts">Artifacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_books">Books</string>
    <string name="title_activity_checkout">Checkout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="title_activity_membership">Membership</string>


    <!--shopping-->
    <string name="shopping_Clothes">Clothes</string>
    <string name="shopping_artifacts">Artifacts</string>
    <string name="shopping_Books">Books</string>
    <!--clothes-->
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Men">MEN</string>
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Men_Item_Info">MEN T-SHIRT\nPRICE : $18</string>
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Women">WOMEN</string>
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Women_Item_Info">Women T-SHIRT\nPRICE : $18</string>
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Kids">KIDS</string>
    <string name="shopping_clothes_Kid_Item_Info">Kid T-SHIRT\nPRICE : $18</string>
    <string name="shopping_artifacts_title">ARTIFACTS</string>
    <string name="shopping_artifacts_Item_Info">ARTIFACTS\nPRICE : $18</string>
    <string name="shopping_details_title">Details</string>
    <string name="shopping_details_orderBtn">Order</string>
    <string name="shopping_details_price">PRICE : $18</string>
    <string name="shopping_details_info">A T-shirt (or t shirt, or tee) is a style of unisex fabric shirt named after the T shape of its body and sleeves. It normally has short sleeves and a round neckline, known as a crew neck, which lacks a collar. T-shirts are generally made of a light, inexpensive fabric and are easy to clean.</string>



    <!--shipping-->
    <string name="shipping_total">TOTAL</string>
    <string name="shipping_subTotal">Sub-total</string>
    <string name="shipping_price">$18.00</string>
    <string name="shipping_Checkout">CHECKOUT</string>
    <string name="shipping_accepted">WE ACCEPT:</string>


    <!--Quiz-->
    <string name="quiz_word">QUIZ NO.1</string>
    <string name="quiz">How old was Tutankamun when died?</string>
    <string name="quiz_answer_i">16 YEARS OLD</string>
    <string name="quiz_answer_ii">18 YEARS OLD</string>
    <string name="quiz_answer_iii">19 YEARS OLD</string>

    <!--membership-->
    <string name="membership_benefits">Membership Benefits</string>
    <string name="Memebership_student">students</string>
    <string name="Memebership_egyptian">Egyptian</string>
    <string name="Memebership_foreign">Foreign</string>

    <string name="membership_benefits_items"><itme>&#8226; Free express admission for you and children under 18.</itme>
        <itme>\n&#8226; Free admission for your guest(s) on every visit.</itme>
        <itme>\n&#8226; Early access to exhibitions and special viewing hours.</itme>
        <itme>\n&#8226; Invitation to buy ticket to members only events and parties.</itme>
        <itme>\n&#8226; 10% off at the Dining room at GEM.</itme>
        <itme>\n&#8226; 10% off at GEM store.</itme>
    </string>
    <string name="choose_category">Choose Category</string>
    <string name="membership_duration">Duration</string>
    <string name="membership_duration_items_i">3 Months</string>
    <string name="membership_duration_items_ii">6 Months</string>
    <string name="membership_duration_items_iii">1 Year</string>



    <string name="related_Links">RELATED</string>
    <!-- login activity -->
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="username">User Name</string>
    <string name="Password">Password </string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget your password</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>

    <!-- registration activity -->
    <string name="signup">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="nationality">Nationlaity</string>
    <string name="go">GO</string>


    <!-- today's event fragment -->

    <!-- event 1-->
    <string name="event1_time">1:00PM</string>
    <string name="event1_topic">King Tutankhamun</string>
    <string name="event1_note">Free Event</string>

    <!-- event 2-->
    <string name="event2_time">3:00PM</string>
    <string name="event2_topic">Art and Decoration in Ancient Egypt</string>
    <string name="event2_note">Paid Event</string>

    <!-- event 3-->
    <string name="event3_time">5:00PM</string>
    <string name="event3_topic">3D Movie of Tutankamun</string>
    <string name="event3_note">For Kids</string>

    <!-- event 4-->
    <string name="event4_time">6:00PM</string>
    <string name="event4_topic">Nefertiti</string>
    <string name="event4_note">Guided Tour</string>
    `
    <!-- event 5-->
    <string name="event5_time">8:00PM</string>
    <string name="event5_topic">Narmer</string>
    <string name="event5_note">Guided Tour</string>

    <!-- event 6-->
    <string name="event6_time">8:00PM</string>
    <string name="event6_topic">Hor-Aha</string>
    <string name="event6_note">Guided Tour</string>


    <!-- for member  fragment -->

    <!-- event 1-->
    <string name="member_event1_time">Nov 04</string>
    <string name="member_event1_topic">Shopping Event</string>
    <string name="member_event1_note">For Members Only</string>

    <!-- event 2-->
    <string name="member_event2_time">Nov 06</string>
    <string name="member_event2_topic">Private Guided Tour</string>
    <string name="member_event2_note">For Members Only</string>


    <!-- event 3-->
    <string name="member_event3_time">Nov 12</string>
    <string name="member_event3_topic">Private Guided Tour</string>
    <string name="member_event3_note">For Members Only</string>


    <!-- featured events  fragment -->

    <!-- event 1-->
    <string name="featured_event1_time">DEC 05</string>
    <string name="featured_event1_topic">Ancient Egyptian Art</string>
    <string name="featured_event1_note">Guided Tour</string>


    <!-- event 2-->
    <string name="featured_event2_time">DEC 10</string>
    <string name="featured_event2_topic">Music in Old Egypt</string>
    <string name="featured_event2_note">Guided Tour</string>


    <!-- event 3-->
    <string name="featured_event3_time">DEC 15</string>
    <string name="featured_event3_topic">King Khufu Tour</string>
    <string name="featured_event3_note">Guided Tour</string>


    <!-- event 4-->
    <string name="featured_event4_time">DEC 18</string>
    <string name="featured_event4_topic">King Tutankhamun Tour</string>
    <string name="featured_event4_note">Guided Tour</string>

    <string name="map_activity_title">Museum Map</string>
    <string name="favourite_title">FAVOURITE</string>
    <string name="tour_activity_title">TOUR PLANNING</string>

    <string name="app_theme">Select Theme</string>

    <string name="temp_text">Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum</string>

    <string name="become_member">Become A MEMBER</string>
    <string name="subscribe">Subscribe</string>

    <string name="gem_pref_key" translatable="false">gem_pref_keys</string>
    <string name="logged_in_key" translatable="false">LOGGED_IN</string>
    <string name="user_id_key" translatable="false">USER_id_KEY</string>
    <string name="user_name_key" translatable="false">USER_NAME_KEY</string>
    <string name="full_name_key" translatable="false">full_NAME_KEY</string>
    <string name="nationality_key" translatable="false">nationality_KEY</string>
    <string name="birth_date_key" translatable="false">birth_date_KEY</string>
    <string name="app_lang_key" translatable="false">language_KEY</string>
    <string name="app_default_lang" translatable="false">en</string>

    <string name="create_tour">Create Tour</string>
    <string name="build_tour">Build Tour</string>
    <string name="select_artifacts">Add artifacts to your tour</string>
    <string name="view_map">View on map</string>
    <string name="start_tour">Start Tour</string>
    <string name="tour_criteria">Build Tour Based On.</string>
    <string name="added_artifacts">Added Artifacts</string>
    <string name="invite_users">Invite</string>
    <string name="select_tour_guide">Select Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="get_tour">Request Tour Guide</string>


    <string name="facebook_app_id">781532365370297</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb781532365370297</string>

    <!-- Tab Names -->
    <string name="visit_tab">Visit</string>
    <string name="highlight_tab">Highlight</string>
    <string name="today_event">Today Event</string>
    <string name="for_members_tab">For Members</string>
    <string name="staff_picks_tab">Staff Picks</string>
    <string name="featured_events_tab">Featured Events</string>
    <string name="going_event">Going</string>

    <string name="individual_tour">Individual</string>
    <string name="group_tour">Group</string>
    <string name="tour_guide">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="tour_name">Tour Name</string>
    <string name="shortest_path">Shortest Path</string>
    <string name="oldest">Oldest</string>

    <string name="individual_tour_title">Create Individual Tour</string>
    <string name="group_tour_title">Create Group Tour</string>
    <string name="tour_guide_title">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="add_users">Add</string>

</resources>
